We all know that having too much work and too much stress can lead to burnout, but did you know that the opposite can also be a problem?
我们都知道工作量过大、压力过大会导致精疲力竭，但你知道吗，相反的情况也可能是一个问题？
Have you ever felt that your job was too easy and that everything was just a bit too boring?
你是否曾觉得自己的工作太轻松，一切都有些太无聊？
If so, you might be suffering from rust out.
如果是这样，你可能正在遭受职业倦怠的困扰。
Rust out happens when there isn't enough challenge to motivate you to keep going in your job.
职业倦怠发生在工作中缺乏足够的挑战来激励你持续前进的时候。
Without some challenge, it can be hard to feel growth in your role.
没有一些挑战，就很难感受到自己在岗位上的成长。
If a job has lots of repetitive and monotonous tasks, it can make it hard to see the purpose of a role.
如果一份工作有很多重复且单调的任务，就很难看清一个岗位的意义。
Having a lower level of responsibility at work than before can also make it harder to feel fulfilled in a job.
工作中的责任水平比以前低，也会让人更难在工作中感到有成就感。
This can affect people who have taken time out from their career for family or personal reasons.
这可能会影响到那些因家庭或个人原因而职业中断的人。
If you think that you might be suffering from rust out, then there are a number of signs to watch out for.
如果你认为自己可能正遭受职业倦怠的困扰，那么有一些迹象需要注意。
You might dread finding your schedule each week and not seeing anything stimulating on it.
你可能会害怕看到每周的日程安排，上面没有任何令人兴奋的内容。
It might be that you often find yourself clock-watching at work, willing the time to pass.
你可能经常在工作中盯着时钟盼下班，希望时间快点过去。
Focus and motivation can drop, leading you to get less done than you had before, or to make more mistakes.
注意力和积极性会下降，导致你比以前完成的工作更少，或者犯更多的错误。
You may start to feel apathetic and disengaged towards your job.
你可能会开始对自己的工作感到冷漠和疏离。
These feelings can lead to anxiety and depression which can then spread from work into people's personal lives.
这些感受可能导致焦虑和抑郁，然后从工作蔓延到人们的个人生活中。
Finding yourself suffering from rust out can sometimes be an opportunity.
发现自己正遭受职业倦怠的困扰有时也可能是一个机会。
Some experts suggest that self-awareness is key.
一些专家建议，自我意识是关键。
By taking some time to realise what you are really looking for in work and life, you can take steps to re-discover your motivation.
花些时间意识到自己在工作和生活中真正想要的是什么，你就可以采取措施重新发现自己的动力。
Setting yourself goals and allowing yourself to try new things can help you find a new purpose.
给自己设定目标，允许自己尝试新事物，可以帮助你找到新的意义。
Considering what you really need for a job can also lead you to find a new one that's better suited to your goals in life.
考虑一份工作你真正需要什么，也可以引导你找到一份更适合你人生目标的新工作。